<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Copyright (c) 2016 Felipe Escoto (https://github.com/Philip-Scott/Spice-up) -->
<component type="desktop">
  <id>com.github.philip-scott.spice-up.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <name>Spice-Up</name>
  <summary>Create simple and beautiful presentations</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Everything you need to create simple and beautiful presentations with text, images, and shapes. Add some spice to your presentations with a wide variety of background patterns and beautiful color palette.
    </p>
    <p>
      Features Include:
    </p>
    <ul>
      <li>Exporting to PDF!</li>
      <li>Presentation Browser: Scroll through the presentations you have made and jump right into them with one click!.</li>
      <li>Controller Support: If you have a USB or Bluetooth controller, plug it in and control your slides!</li>
      <li>Templates, so you can whip up a presentation in a blink of an eye.</li>
      <li>You can edit images in your favorite editor, and it will automatically update when saved</li>
      <li>Open Spice-Up files from a web browser by drag and drop if the app is not installed!</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <provides>
    <binary>spice-up</binary>
  </provides>
  <releases>
    <release version="1.3.0" date="2018-2-2">
      <description>
        <p>The Color Update</p>
        <ul>
          <li>The color picker has had a mayor makeover!</li>
          <li>You can now add/remove stops in gradients, as well as move them around and rotate them.</li>
          <li>Grab inspiration from one of the ten new gradient presets!</li>
          <li>You can also pick colors from the screen.</li>
          <li>Fonts are search-able now</li>
          <li>Font-styles are now styled (pun intended)</li>
          <li>Notifications are now disabled when presenting</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.2.0" date="2017-12-25">
      <description>
        <p>Presents for Presenters!</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Presentation View! Starting a presentation with two monitors will open the presentation on the secondary monitor, and a presentation viewer on your main screen.</li>
          <li>You can now type presenter notes, and see them while presenting!</li>
          <li>Your presentations now end with an all-black slide</li>
          <li>Images can now be added by Drag and Drop</li>
          <li>Spice-Up is now available in Serbian!</li>
          <li>Some other fixes and cleanups</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.1.0" date="2017-11-2">
      <description>
        <p>Huge Success!</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Presentations saved can now be viewed from a web browser by drag and drop if Spice-Up is not installed, and even if you're not using elementary OS or Linux</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.0.1" date="2017-10-13">
      <description>
        <p>I'm making a note here...</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Lots of optimizations have happened, now it loads presentations crazy fast!</li>
          <li>The Text Toolbar has been cleaned up to better match the other bars</li>
          <li>You can now align text vertically!</li>
          <li>Going to and from the Welcome Screen is now animated</li>
          <li>Spice-Up is now translated to French and Portuguese!</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.0.0" date="2017-09-14">
      <description>
        <p>This was a triumph!</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Creating a new presentation now brings up templates you can choose from.</li>
          <li>You can now replace images right from Spice-Up.</li>
          <li>Making a new slide now picks up the style from your last one.</li>
          <li>You can now make Text and Shapes transparent, right from the custom color picker!</li>
          <li>Fixed: Double clicking would sometimes unselect the item.</li>
          <li>Fixed: The text on the roundness slider was hard to read.</li>
          <li>Spice-Up is also now available in Spanish!</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.8.2" date="2017-08-27">
      <description>
        <p>Now with 100% better feedback!</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Selecting slides, and colors on the color picker now feels like you actually press something.</li>
          <li>ColorPicker: Click on the preview to be able to set both colors at once.</li>
          <li>A better high resolution icon</li>
          <li>Fixed: Spice-Up should now work a lot better with other themes</li>
          <li>Fixed: Sometimes, the default blue color would get selected</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.8.0" date="2017-07-20">
      <description>
        <p>Clipboard, Circles and a Browser</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Shapes: You can now set the roundness of the square, and finally make circles!</li>
          <li>Cut, copy, and paste slides, and canvas items!</li>
          <li>The presentations you make will appear on the welcome screen for easy access to them!</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Philip-Scott/Spice-up/master/Screenshot.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Philip-Scott/Spice-up/master/Screenshot1.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Philip-Scott/Spice-up/master/Screenshot2.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Philip-Scott/Spice-up/master/Screenshot3.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Philip-Scott/Spice-up/master/Screenshot4.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <developer_name>Felipe Escoto</developer_name>
  <url type="homepage">https://github.com/Philip-Scott/Spice-up</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/Philip-Scott/Spice-up/issues</url>
  <url type="help">https://github.com/Philip-Scott/Spice-up/issues</url>
  <update_contact>felescoto@hotmail.com</update_contact>
  <custom>
    <value key="x-appcenter-color-primary">#C2D5FF</value>
    <value key="x-appcenter-color-primary-text">#223b69</value>
  </custom>
</component>
